[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2007 the Muslims in the world outnumbered the Christians.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What director worked on the 1991 movie Thelma  Louise?", "correct_answer": "Ridley Scott", "incorrect_answers": ["Quentin Tarantino", "Martin Scorsese", "Oliver Stone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1863 this entrepreneur and his partners founded Standard Oil, a company which dominated oil production in the USA for decades.", "correct_answer": "John Rockefeller", "incorrect_answers": ["Howard Hughes", "Jean Paul Getty", "Andrew Carnegie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "As the head of the Japanese Secret Service, this character uses a private subway system under the streets of Tokyo, in the James Bond movie, You Only Live Twice.", "correct_answer": "Tiger Tanaka", "incorrect_answers": ["Hiraku Hashimoto", "Yasuhiro Yoshida", "Senjei Suzuki"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The culture of physics research differs from the other sciences in the separation of these two.", "correct_answer": "Theory and experiment", "incorrect_answers": ["Abstract and real", "Microscopic and macroscopic", "Visible and invisible"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of fat is used for the preparation of the popular Chiffon cake?", "correct_answer": "Butter", "incorrect_answers": ["No fat is used", "Vegetable oil", "Palm oil"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The valleys of the Yellow River and the Pearl River are two of the seven main national valleys in this country.", "correct_answer": "China", "incorrect_answers": ["Burma", "Thailand", "India"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many books are in the Jewish Torah?", "correct_answer": "5", "incorrect_answers": ["7", "2", "3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of eyes does Dr. Loomis say Michael had in the 1978 Halloween movie?", "correct_answer": "the Devils eyes", "incorrect_answers": ["blackened eyes", "hopeless eyes", "dead eyes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what Asian country did one of the two main branches of alchemy originate?", "correct_answer": "China", "incorrect_answers": ["India", "Saudi Arabia", "Japan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This US National Park, famous for its mineral waters, is located in southeastern Oklahoma, near the city of Sulphur.", "correct_answer": "Platt", "incorrect_answers": ["Hot Springs", "Yellowstone", "Mesa Verde"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This animation firm created movies such as Toy Story (1995), Monsters, Inc. (2001) and the award-winning The Incredibles (2004).", "correct_answer": "Pixar Animation Studios", "incorrect_answers": ["Walt Disney Feature Animation", "JibJab", "DreamWorks Animation"]}]